so we are in week four of making history
in 60 days I'm gonna turn these hundred
dollars into a million dollars
absolutely everything is going to be
documented here on my YouTube on my
telegram Discord Instagram so not only
you guys can see the journey but also
learn and copy from me all of the trades
before I take it they're gonna take it
after I take it you guys are going to
see it here on YouTube every single week
and it's going to be audited account so
you guys can verify everything that I do
we started two weeks ago and I ended up
blowing through the first account when I
took my first attempt at this chapter
and then from there we restarted from
zero where then we turned the hundred
dollars into twenty one hundred dollars
and then we turn the 2100 into forty one
hundred dollars in the week after that
so join me as you make history now on
week four of the challenge let's get
started
all right it is week four we're gonna be
turning this four thousand dollars into
ten thousand dollars by the end of this
week I don't need a chair this week
because I'm hyper coming in let me show
you guys exactly what I'm gonna be
looking for so you guys can follow on
every single trade because no more of
that slow [__] all right let's get into
it as you guys can tell this is
currently your GBP as you guys can see
up here your GDP this is going to be our
full watch list for this week but I'm
just gonna break down the top three so
your GBP we have this very strong level
of resistance that is going to be
potentially used as support you guys
remember your GDP we caught this by we
caught this by and we caught this bike
we're just gonna keep buying because the
market is heading to the upside so
whenever we are under this Market we're
heading down we're heading down whenever
we're under heading down whenever we're
under heading down so whenever we're
above we should be heading to the upside
so what I'm going to be waiting for to
enter this trade right here is going to
be literally what is drawn right here a
break to the upside a retest so then go
long on this trade very simple next we
got GDP cut so last week this trade
right here gave us a lot of headache but
obviously made us money which is a good
thing so as of right now we are waiting
for the same exact thing as your GBP
we're going to be waiting for a simple
break retest and then to go down on this
area because we are bullish on all time
frames as well you can tell here we are
bullish on The Daily on the weekly and
on the four hours so the most logical
thing would be to buy so I'm going to
simply be waiting for is for this price
from here to have a push retest and then
go long next we have AUD JPY which AUB
JPY it is looking very solid because
once again the weekly time frame daily
time frame and the four hour time frame
are all headed to the upside so if all
of the markets are headed to the upside
like this the most logical thing is to
Simply buy so this is where I'm going
down to the four hour time frame and
this is exactly what I'm going to be
waiting for I'm going to be waiting for
price to then dip above this area right
here have a retest and then head to the
outside I'm not going to do anything
under this Zone because I you can tell
whenever we're under we're selling and
we want to buy with the trend and then
last but not least we have nzd USD which
I'm simply going to be waiting for the
same exact move right here break retest
and then push as you can tell right here
I'm just going to get the same previous
price action and replicate it right here
as you can see the retest would be
perfectly to this area of Interest where
then we'll be looking to enter a sell
trade at this area right here so those
are the markets for this week let me
show you guys the starting balance of
the account because I'm feeling very
very very confident this week that if
you take two solid trades we can easily
flip it to ten thousand so this is the
currently starting balance of the
account
4160 so I'm probably gonna risk half of
the account maybe a little bit more than
half on the first trade that I take this
week obviously high risk but it's gonna
pay off so
um no trades for tonight it's obviously
the first lemon session of the night it
is 10 33 on Sunday so we're gonna
probably do trades tomorrow morning in
New York so I'll catch you guys tomorrow
thank you
what is up guys so it is currently right
now Monday morning 9 10 in the morning
as of right now so we avoided a loss
simply by sticking to our plan so let me
show you exactly what I mean by that
well as a right now you guys can tell we
are still currently in no open trades
right now in the account we are still
the same exact balance and this is Euro
GBP so as you guys can tell yesterday we
were anticipating for price to then
break above this area to then read this
and go long we never broke above the
area of Interest so we never took the
trade this is the importance of waiting
for the break of the area of interest
that was our number one pair for the
week next one is GBP CAD as you guys can
tell here same exact thing we're simply
waiting for the break and retest above
this area of interest in order to take
the trade long we never got it don't
take the trade it is that simple next we
have AUD JPY which we did have a
beautiful reaction from this area right
here and now what I'm going to be
waiting for on the one hour time frame
is I'm going to be waiting for inverted
Head and Shoulders which is going to be
a left a head and then a right shoulder
so basically what I'm doing is that I am
waiting for a pullback to this area to
take the trade to the upside so we
already did this right we already had
this beautiful push and I get this and I
put it right here kind of crazy
obviously exact same size but um you
guys can look at the recording
information like I did not edit that so
we already had this break right here so
now what we are going to anticipate is
this pullback into this area of Interest
so then we can continue to have the
lungs to the upside and then last but
not least on the next pair that I am
interested in it's going to be nzd USD
which I'm simply going to continue to
wait for the pool back to this level
right here in order to take the trade to
the downside I mean you got to the
downside and then your JPY I'm going to
be waiting for this little quick retest
of this area right here in order to take
the trade to the outside so loads of
opportunity in the market it is still
just Monday morning we're just getting
started I'm glad that we started off the
week avoiding a loss because this just
makes me me a thousand times more
confident and not only my strategy but
in the approach of the market that is
being patient and waiting for a good
quality trade setup so right now it is
currently 9 12 in the morning Monday so
we're gonna wait probably another hour
to see what happens and I'll update you
guys then all right so trade update I
think it's two and a half or three and a
half hours later or probably a little
bit more right so we got into the AUD
JPY trade so let me show you exactly how
we got in which is exactly what I
explained let me show you guys all right
so as you guys can see here these are
the AUD JPY Longs that I predicted as
you guys can tell currently live on both
of these trades so when we go here to
the charts it is exactly what I
explained we're gonna have this pullback
to the right shoulder Candlestick is his
textbook trade right here um we're just
gonna keep setting and forgetting
holding the trade auditor take profit
which is going to be a one to two point
six risk reward and um breaking very
solid as of right now we are about 700
went relatively low risk on this trade I
have a pretty big stop loss um and then
update on the other trades so your GDP
we broke up up this zone right here so
we never broke above we simply never
took the trade and then GBP CAD we are
currently breaking Above This zone so
I'm going to be looking to enter lungs
once and if we end up breaking above
that zone so just a quick a little
refresh right now it is currently August
14 12 35 in the afternoon so so far
looking good
um
Marcus said she's probably going to get
a little bit slow right now because you
know it's already gonna leave this
session but we're gonna eat and then
probably hit the gym pick up the drift
car maybe and I will update you guys on
the trade as we go all right so trade up
there right now Market hasn't moved much
let me show you guys what I mean as you
guys can tell this is still the same
exact AUD JPY trade
um I am expecting price to have a little
bit of a pullback and retest the
neckline of the head and shoulders so to
retest this zone right here I have a
little pullback before continue heading
to the upside um but as of right now the
trade is pretty much a little bit more
in profit we're a little bit higher I
guess with those Wicks and then GBP CAD
we are still heading to the upside who
I'm waiting for the brake and retest so
everything Still Remains exactly the
same we're gonna pull up now to uh a
merch shop I guess I did whatever we're
gonna make like 500 rocket 21 shirts
some seven figure shirts a little bit of
everything so whenever we do the meet
and greets we just give them out to
people or just give it like our students
away for free so we're gonna pull it
right now into the shop all right market
update it is currently seven o'clock at
night we still have the trade running in
profit I'm going to show you guys what I
predict to happen either tonight in
London or tomorrow in the morning so we
capitalize after this move so let me
show you right now as you can tell this
is currently how the account is looking
remember all we have to do is flip it to
10 000 by the end of the week so if I
close right now we'd be halfway but I
still want to hold the trade probably
the string can make us anywhere from
like three to thirty five hundred so let
me show you guys so this is right here
AUD JPY which is the trade that we are
currently in right now we entered at
this level right here I love how the
daily Candlestick has closed which is a
very strong daily bullish pin bar I do
expect for the next daily Candlestick to
have a pool bike into this level to then
retest that EMA if we retest the EMA we
would then come back and also
potentially be retesting this uh four
hour EMA as well and if we go down to
the lower time frame like the one hour
we would also be retesting the one hour
EMA which would be this level right here
and on top of that we'd be retesting the
neckline of the head and shoulders so
I'm going to be looking to add positions
if we do pull back into this area area
and if we have any rejection
candlesticks from this area for me to
add a position so I'm definitely still
going to keep holding AUD JPY next we
have GBP CAD which you've had a very
strong daily bullish pin bar rejection
from the zone I'm just going to simply
be waiting for the same exact thing that
I've been waiting for all week which is
a break and retest above this area to go
long and then Euro GBP we are no longer
interested because we've had a longer
projection than we should have so for
now you're a GBP and no longer
interested in I'm gonna put nzd USD on
top of it which is going to give us our
pullback into this area so we're
expecting for price to come back into
here so we continue to take the cells to
the downside so that right now this is
how we are currently looking and we're
just waiting for that pullback so the
only trade we are currently in right now
is AUD JPY uh we're going to look to add
positions here very soon and GBP CAD
once it breaks and read this above so as
of right now to show you guys real time
it is Monday 7 o'clock at night so
probably in the next the Market's not
going to do anything for like the next
three four hours so pre-lum then I'll
update you guys if there's anything if
not tomorrow in the morning so check
back with you guys very soon
[Applause]
music
[Music]
so we're gonna go shoot some flames
right now we got a little bit of blue
you probably were filling the blue blue
one more blue let me make sure it's blue
blue ish so we're gonna go through some
flames right now I'm filling this thing
up right now and I can guarantee you by
the time we get back home it's gonna
have half a tank this is the car that
has wasted the most gas that I've ever
owned in my whole entire life so let's
go see some with some flame let's see
what Flames this car could actually do
[Music]
gas update not trade update half a tank
we just filled it up probably drove for
like what like 20 minutes hit like like
100 pops half tank trigger lifestyle
what is up guys so it is Tuesday Morning
nine in the morning and exactly what I
said yesterday has happened in the
markets today and once again a little
bit too much sudden forget got to us but
this right here is going to be a very
valuable lesson so I'm going to show you
guys how we have to stick to the plan so
let me show you guys how the trade is
looking and what we expect to happen
today all right so as you guys can tell
this is the AUD JPY trade we were in
yesterday as of right now we are now
floating about 190 in profit so as you
guys can see yesterday's prediction how
we were around this area right here I'll
explain to you guys how we needed a
retest of the neckline or The Head and
Shoulders retest of the EMA in order to
go along and then this trade I was
looking around here last night and we
were actually up 2500 where the account
was sitting at almost seven thousand
dollars and I didn't close because I
strongly believe we were going to
continue to break to the upside but we
weren't at my take profit either so I'm
not mad at it I I don't consider that
great because the trade wasn't complete
so as of right now the trade has now
pulled all the way back back into our
entry level whereas now giving us
another bullish engulfing Candlestick
rejection from this area of interest of
the head and shoulders and exactly what
I explained yesterday how we were going
to create that daily Wick we're testing
that EMA so I am strongly considering
adding another position literally as we
speak right now so I will be updating
you guys if I do in the next 15 minutes
and then next we have GBP CAD which I
explained yesterday how the only way I
would look to take this trade long is if
we break above and retest and it has
done that perfectly as I explained
yesterday hundreds of Traders on my
Instagram caught this live with me along
with the Traders in my free telegram you
guys can see it right here in my free
telegram currently have almost 70 000
members completely for free I gave the
trade idea of GBP CAD yesterday this was
yesterday at 7 00 PM EST uh waiting for
the break-in retest to go along and
would you look at that I didn't manage
to catch this train because I just my
focus wasn't on here and honestly I was
sleeping so it is what it is but
retested perfectly if this trade comes
back into this area for any reason it
gives me any other entry I will be
adding a position very soon so this is
how we're currently looking on AUD JPY
where I might be adding a new entry very
very soon oh and just so you guys can
see it is currently 908 in the morning
Tuesday Morning Miami time not sure why
it's working but you guys can see it so
as of right now we're gonna see if we
add another entry in AUD JPY and then
we're going to see if we hopefully
entered GBP card and it gives us another
entry so showing you guys how once again
we predicted the market not only to have
the push but then the retest and the
push once again so let's see if we could
bring a big bit once again so we could
get another entry into it so I'll update
you guys in the next hours all right so
it is currently 10 30 in the morning
market update trade and ah one of those
trades so let me show you guys so we are
currently back into drawdown on this
trade as you can tell right now we are
kind of swinging up and down with the
trade to see if we go to break even or
not but I'm gonna keep it at the plan
and I'm gonna keep sending forgetting
and then this trade right here happens
so beautiful damn but we missed the
whole trade literally predicted to break
the retest and the push to the upside
the Perfection but I didn't manage to
get an entry on it and the one that I
did enter is doing this right now but it
happens guys we're gonna enter the trade
hopefully back I break even and then
we're gonna see exactly what happened so
I'll update you guys in the next hour
hopefully we don't get stopped out all
right so update I think like 15 minutes
later let me show you guys exactly what
the trade is right now and exactly
basically what I explained set and
forget so right now you guys can see how
the trade is currently now almost at
break even or we're just down about 130
bucks huge rejection from the area of
Interest this is like I've always said
the importance of having a solid area
Venture so I'm gonna debate uh whether I
close and re-enter off of another
engulfing or how this Candlestick is
going to keep heading to the upside if
this Candlestick engulfs on top of all
of these I will then be adding entries
to this position all right so trade up
there right now as you guys can tell it
is 12 o'clock on the market and I got
into the trade that I explained that I
was going to get in and then we are back
in positive and the one that we were in
drawdown like 700 if you guys just saw a
second ago but let me explain to you
guys what happened so basically what
happened is that we were just creating a
very long Wick we were just creating
this huge Wick rejection and obviously
down here we were in the red we had the
bullish engulfing how I explained were
going to happen which is exactly where
then I decided to enter this new
position after that area so currently we
are in this position right here which we
are up 260 dollars which is this one and
then AUD JPY which we are pretty much
Break Even probably in the last now
which is this one so we're gonna update
you guys uh how the market moves in the
next couple of hours and um probably
slow right now because the market volume
is going to go down but you never know
so we'll update you guys
thank you
all right so trade up there right now
we're at the gym
it happens we're currently a little bit
in drought on the trade I think right
now what we're going to do is we're
going to create that four hour wig to
touch that EMA two hour looks okay one
hour look okay 30 minute looks okay
we got the boy John here
he's right the 30 minute looks good all
right so trade up there right now I just
finished eating a sandwich right now
we're gonna be fine so I don't like how
this Candlestick is moving right now but
as of right now this Candlestick is very
very bearish but I'm going to keep
keeping my eye on it because
we still have potential I'll update you
guys in three four hours when the daily
Candlestick closes so we still got some
time so I'll catch you guys then all
right so market update it is currently
10 37 at night and stop loss was hit oh
I hate when this happens because I was
up in the trade almost 2500 and it comes
all the way back and then it hits my
stop-loss I hate when this happens but
it's part of the process because it
didn't hit my final take profit I'm not
gonna let these 10 these type of things
get to me but it just like puts me out
of like the actual Rhythm that I have
for the challenge so now I'm down I'm
just going to show you guys and I'll
explain all right so as you guys can see
this is where the account is right now
three thousand four hundred dollars you
know we took about like a 800 loss as
you can see right here it is the same
thing three thousand four hundred
dollars so annoying you can see the p l
come down a little bit you can see right
now the losses there was a 755 loss and
then on top of that you can also see how
now our win rate is at a 55 you're
taking a total of 11 trades ah this is
so annoying but I mean it's part of the
process so I'm going to explain to you
guys exactly what happened so other than
the trade hitting the stop loss it is
what it is I strongly still do believe
this trade can head to the upside I'm
just going to be waiting for a break and
retest of this area so if you noticed
the market is trending to the upside I'm
just gonna wait for a breaker retest so
this trade right here I'm gonna wait for
it to do something like this in order to
actually be able to enter the trade long
so the trade hit my full stop loss but I
closed it out a little bit above it if
you see right here price started having
this pullback and I always like to close
a trade for this specific challenge
before we enter a session so we're not
in a session I'm just gonna get out
because I know when we enter a session
it's going to do all this and work us
out so I entered right at that line
right there but I like to document
everything I have everything very
specific so adjpy we're gonna be waiting
for a break and retest to then go long
next we have GBP CAD where we have the
bullish push to the upside beautiful
daily bullish engulfing Candlestick so
I'm going to be waiting for a wick pool
back into this area to then go along we
notice we're just waiting for a retest
of this area to bengalang we already had
this break so now I'm just simply
waiting for this pullback to take the
straight lung and then nzd USB has now
given us any opportunity so my only main
focus right now is GBP Cad and AED JPY
and as you guys can tell if I refresh
the time here it is currently Tuesday 10
40 p.m so we're about to enter London
session I mean it's just annoying
because it puts us back a little bit but
I always say this like everything
happens for a reason maybe this avoided
me to double down my risk even more on
it and this is what it's going to do is
it's just going to make me more sharp to
take a trade I haven't broken any rules
everything is going according to plan
it's just a simple loss you can't avoid
losses when trading they're inevitable
that's why I have very smart risk
management in place if you notice I
didn't blow the account but I did risk
almost a 33 of the account because I'm
risking high so we can obviously scale
to complete this challenge I'll just
check anything later on today in London
or tomorrow in the morning but I think
if we get some some nice trade setups on
GBP CAD we can still hit the 10K by the
end of the week
what is up guys so market update which
is basically the next morning which is 9
50 in the morning and exactly what I
explained yesterday was going to happen
to the tea exactly so let's check it out
so as you guys can see here we have all
three phones bro the Galaxy is always
updating I don't know why but we got
into the adjpy trade exactly as I
explained we're already up what I lost
yesterday in those two little workouts
and you can see here that the market
literally Wicked this out perfectly man
and these things are going to happen it
is literally inevitable that the market
will just hit your stop loss and then
start heading back in your direction
there's absolutely nothing you can do
and it's okay because this just means
that all you have to do is just adjust
your stop-loss a little bit over the
next period of 10 trades but what
matters is that we are right about the
direction as a whole so as of right now
this is currently how we are looking it
did exactly what it said yesterday we're
gonna break above this area and then
retest it to go long so this is exactly
what we're doing right here this is the
brake this is the retest and now we are
heading to the upside very confident
that this trade will continue to head to
the upside as long as this hourly
Candlestick right here manages to close
above this structure point right here if
that closes above that structure point
in the next eight minutes which is right
here as you can see the Candlestick time
then this trade will have loads of
upside potential so I will be looking to
scale in if I get any opportunities
after that but I am in a very nice
position as of right now so this is my
only focus GBP card it has never pulled
back into the area of Interest predicted
this beautifully just didn't manage to
get an entry my entry would have been
something like this this is how I would
be improv from the trade but couldn't
manage to do it so we are still in AUD
JPY and as of right now we are currently
floating around a thousand three hundred
dollars in profit so I'll teach you guys
in the next upcoming out all right guys
so trade update don't mind the clean
lady in the back trade break even went a
little bit into drop down but it's
loading up I might add some positions
very very soon
so it is currently 3 45 in the afternoon
so the daily campus is about to close
and we are up about 250 dollars this is
how the market is looking right now
price earlier this morning had it pushed
to the upside but if you notice we have
not managed to close above that line how
I mentioned right there um we got about
another hour and a half to see if we can
do it I don't think there's going to be
enough momentum to do so but this daily
Candlestick is looking very good even if
it closes just as it is now it is a
bullish daily pin bar we can anticipate
for them the next day to have a
beautiful fill of the rest of that Wick
right there so that's what I'm expecting
for this tray so I'm going to keep
instead of forgetting and continue to
hold this trade all the way to the
upside and then we have Juniper CAD
which this absolutely took off if I
would have caught this trade I would
have made over ten thousand dollars on
this one single trade like from right
here but didn't manage to get into it
missed it but we predicted it perfect so
slow day in the market really not much
just the market literally went up way
down if you see that the doji the market
hasn't moved so we're just going to set
them forget see what uh pre London
brings in today and we'll check back in
later tonight all right so trade up
there right now it is 6 50 in the
afternoon trade is currently still
around break even so if I show you guys
where the trade is right now it's
literally in the same exact spot so I'm
still very confident that this area is
going to hold up right here so right now
we're in Brickell we're doing a rocket
ad we got rocket and then we got the the
rocket volunteers here we got the boys
bro we got the boys
we're gonna hit a rock ad right now and
then we'll see if the trade is take
profit or stop us I don't care anymore
you traded with your own capital or a
funded account I trade my own capital
you treat your own capital or a funded
account uh uh exactly what I thought
trade with your own Capital you're gonna
end up like that guy trading rocket 21
or you're getting 90 profit split Trader
rocket 21 today all right so right now
we're gonna do a rocket ad with our boy
over here and he's down and get thrown
in because I told him like yo if you
fall into the water for the ad I'm gonna
get you a whole drip right now at soccer
we have our other boy look look how wet
everything is like look how everything
is he already fell into the water like
pizza floor look at the floor full of
water so our boys next you're gonna do
our boy next so this is the guy that he
already jumped into the water big
commitment look at him look at him soggy
socks they're trading now I'm gonna get
them all drift out right now sax Fair
committing trade update trade update
you have a personal account or a funded
account what are you funded with
if you're enjoying rocket 21 you're
gonna end up under the water like that
guy during rocket 21 today so you get a
90 profit split on your funded account
during rocket 21. all right so we just
finished the ad right now for Rockets
anyone
these guys got wet the commitment is
real so we're gonna take him to Saks now
get him some drip because bro these guys
deserve it bro appreciate it
and they're both
let's go get some drip imagine a clip of
a clip of how many times I say the word
said I forget you could probably do a
clip of like an hour more than nightly
you make a song out of what I said you
added me and that's like three days
so I don't forget shorts underwear socks
shoes
she's got a shirt
it's about to be cold as [__] in sex
right now so I feel bad for them bro
it's about to be so cold all right
they're gonna do whatever you guys want
let's get it over here whatever you guys
want let's do it right there's no
there's no Dior
look at jeans and shirt whatever you
guys want
this that yes bro now you analyze the
charts with that dude
[Music]
I mean but I was going to talk about
like these guys they're Traders and when
we did the lambo giveaway I'm like yo we
need volunteers who's gonna help us out
these guys helped us out and helped us
out with this ad and he's helped us out
before so like I said I love giving back
to the community World during rocket 21
or swing training lab how are we looking
full new man over here the boys dripped
out you guys ready yeah I gotta check
out like this we saved them they were
ready to run out looking fresh my boy
all right guys so this is what happens
when you make 15K trading and you don't
know what to do with it y'all here
Center forget page
[Music]
this is legit my first designer whatever
like uh
welcome to the club
foreign
six hundred dollars this is basically
where we started the account last week
this type of thing happens and what
pisses me off let me explain to you guys
right so this is exactly what happened
yesterday yesterday I got whipped out
and then we went back into profit
luckily we closed this trade not in that
much of a loss so it's like an 800 loss
but now this one it completely stopped
us out for a full loss and we lost this
one completely so we were completely
wrong about this trade I don't mind this
loss but I hate the wick outs plus the
actual loss it is what it is and then on
top of that we missed this monster on
gpp CAD that right now we would have
been up almost a one to four risk to
reward which would have given us as of
right now a total of about a hundred
Pips which is insane but these type of
things have to happen and not that they
happen these type of things are very
normal in the market like obviously my
goal is to flip this account but if the
market doesn't give me good
probabilities like just absolutely
nothing that I can do but it's still
Wednesday and I still see one night's
potential trade GBP USDA can give us a
nice sell opportunity to make money
tomorrow so let me break it down so this
is where we have GBP USD where we are
currently bearish on this weekly time
frame which is this one daily time frame
is still bullish depends where you put
the higher level what matters to me is
that we are rejecting this daily EMA and
we are rejecting this structure level
right here which is not super strong but
it looks decent on the four hour I like
how in the four hour whenever you are
under your selling whenever you're under
selling whenever you're above you're
buying and as of right now we are under
so in order for me to take this trade
right here I'm going to be looking for
either a pullback into this area right
here to then sell or then I'm going to
be waiting for a break and retest of
this area right here in order for me to
take the cell on this trade so I'm going
to be looking for this or this to enter
this trade to the downside on GBP USD I
would almost enter at this point where
we are right now but I want to be very
conservative and wait for a higher risk
trade and to show you guys the my
effects book because like shows you how
the risk management is key to this trade
so let me show you guys because you guys
can see currently right now the account
is at 2500 the highest we had it was at
4 400 and as of right now you can see
that this week this is what we've lost
today this is what we lost alone and
then whereas right now we have a total
of 12 trades with a 50 50 win rate six
out of the 12 trades or wins six trades
are losses and we are still profitable
so that shows you guys that risk
management is key and then you can see
the p l chart we had the higher high and
then we dip down so I mean this is like
part of trading there's nothing you can
do to avoid this the only thing you can
do to avoid this is have perfect risk
management so you stay in the game and
don't get beat so we're still definitely
in this challenge this is just the
challenging part of it and let's see if
GBP USD gives us a new trade opportunity
I am done with AUD JPY for the week and
then GBP CAD is literally
gone
all right so mark it up there we just
finished trading London last night and
we are tired but sometime training
London in Miami time pays off so let me
show you guys right now the account this
is a train that we caught on gbb CAD so
this is the trade that we missed the
whole entire week literally the one that
we've been missing the long all week and
I'm like you know what why haven't been
trying to get another trade that hasn't
given me any trending signs let's just
go to the trade that is giving us
trending sign let's just hop in on the
next higher low let me show you guys so
this is basically GBP CAD the trade that
we caught remember this is the trade
that we're supposed to be in down here
that we predicted the beautiful break
and then the retest to head to the
upside like this trade was absolutely
beautiful but we couldn't get into the
Australia so last night I always loved
looking at uh the trades right before
London and you guys can see how we have
this area of Interest right here and
when I go down to the one hour this area
of interest is a level of support when
above resistance one under and I see
this beautiful pullback this is the
higher highest the higher low so we're
still bullish we have a beautiful
pullback into here we retest this area
around psychological 7200 so I'm going
to show you guys right here right there
round psychological level of 7200 and
then on top of that we have a one hour
doji rejection from the EMA So I entered
this trade perfectly after this double
Doge candlesticks right here
um not too late but it was perfect it
was at 5 30 in the morning so it was a
perfect trade and as of right now I'm
determining whether I hold or whether I
close because this trade right here has
perfectly brought us back on your
account above it's actually taking us to
the highest and I literally went like
full margin on this trade I'm like you
know what we missed the whole thing
we're gonna get this last tray with a
nice lot size so I'm tired of [__] but
we caught the trade so analyzing the
market further now look at this so this
is a trade that I obviously caught this
inverted Head and Shoulders left head
right shoulder I explained that we're
gonna have the break and then retest so
this is one entry right here that I
missed and we have higher high higher
low this is two entry higher higher low
this is the third entry retest in this
area higher high and then higher low now
at this area this is the fourth entry so
we literally caught the last entry of
the higher high and higher low Trend and
I was all week focusing on another pair
when this was giving me plenty of
opportunity to just take a trade at the
higher low zero drop down zero stress
just trading with the trend so another
very valuable lesson that I learned this
week that is to follow a single pair
that is making the most sense just
because you missed the first entry
doesn't mean you can't get in on another
one there's no need to be greedy or have
like an ego and try to force another
trade when it's not even there and
that's exactly what I've been trying to
do with AUD JPY and let me show you guys
GBP USD which it never aligned with what
I explained yesterday so GBP USD as you
guys can tell I had this lineup right
here to come all the way back to my area
of Interest we never made it back to
that area and we never broke under this
area so we never took the trade and as
we were going up here we were just
heading to the upside so GBP USD same
exact thing I was forcing something
that's not even there and then GBP CAD
is giving us this beautiful full
momentum by simply trading with your
Trend trading with the trend is the
number one conference as of right now
we're gonna currently wait for that
trade to
probably gonna close right now so we
officially closed the trade and good
profit uh it's not that I'm not excited
I'm just tired I've literally probably
slept like two hours this is how the
account is looking right now so we are
at seven thousand dollars on the trade
and let me show you guys the my effects
book to show you guys everything matches
as you guys can see we are up a total of
six thousand percent now so now it is
seven thousand twenty four cents you can
see right here in the piano chart you
can see the dip that we had yesterday
but then today's win brought everything
back up you can tell us the same account
that we've been taking from the 100
bucks to where we are right now and then
now this week we ended up being
positively total of 2 800 from where we
were at the start of the week so back to
13 trades and our win rate is probably
like 55 so that's how we're looking for
this week
um getting a little more excited you
know but done trading for the day I'm
stepping away from the charts all day
and now I'm only going to just focus on
clearing my mind and that is it I'll
probably take a trade later tonight if
anything but I'm trying to take the
account seven thousand to three thousand
so stay tuned all right trade update so
it is Thursday one in the morning so you
guys can see right here it's literally
about to be one the account is in the
exact same spot so I could have actually
continued to hold the trade and I'd
probably be up right now like nine
thousand so let me show you guys so this
is the marker right now let me actually
just refresh the time so you guys can
see the time so it's August 18th one in
the morning so pretty much Friday
already so this is where I ended up
closing the trade this morning I could
have continued to hold to basically
where we are right now but just decided
to get the profits and run could have
entered another position right here at
the break and retest because again
remember the market all it's doing is
just creating higher highs and higher
lows and all I'm doing is entering at
this higher low right here but obviously
the I just didn't want to risk it was
already up and down with the market a
djpy kept going to the downside so we
were completely wrong on this trade
nzdusd never came back into this area to
give us our entry so I don't think I'm
going to be taking any trades tonight
I'd rather just stay out we didn't hit
if I don't take a trade tonight we
didn't hit our 10 okay goal but we did
fit the account we made probably 2K for
this week which is good down 3K from my
original take profit that I'm supposed
to be at but we're still kind of in
schedule to hit the mill in like 60 70
days so we'll teach you guys tomorrow if
I end up taking the training tonight
which I probably won't we'll see where
it goes
so nothing on Friday literally stressful
day I didn't trade anything did it look
at the markets didn't add any positions
I was done because I realized the
mistake that I did and I was only
focusing on AUD JPY when I had plenty of
opportunity at GP cut but not gonna let
that get to me just not trading anymore
for the rest of the week so next week
I'm seeing a lot of opportunity so let's
do a recap of this week so the week
started with the account at 4 100 in
profit and the current status of the
account right now is seven thousand
dollars in profit so this is what
happened so we started off the week with
AUD JPY trade with a loss it took a
second AUD JPY trade and it was a loss
and then we had a third AUD JPY trade
and it was a loss and as I was
monitoring those losses I realized that
I had missed multiple entries on GBP cat
and that is where we came in on Thursday
and we ended up catching a beautiful
continuation by on gpp CAD that made up
our three losses plus profit currently
we're not the challenge I'm down 3 from
where I'm supposed to be I'm supposed to
be at 10 000 on the challenge so I
complete the hundreds of the mill in 60
days so I mean it's really not much and
to some of you guys when you guys see
seven thousand to ten thousand it might
not seem like a lot but this can
completely throw off my trading so it is
very crucial that I continue to hit
those targets because now by the end of
next week I have to be by twenty
thousand dollars but it was a lesson
that I learned this week that is do not
force any trades AUD JPY I was literally
forcing it every single day and I was
distracted by it and not looking at what
matters which is GPU CAD which is a
beautiful trending market so a perfect
lesson for this week is focus on what
matters and trade with the trend if you
notice every single week on every single
one of these videos I have learned the
lesson and I have applied it and I have
either capitalized off of it or avoided
a loss if I keep this going passing this
challenge is not going to be that
difficult because I'm learning from my
mistakes and I'm applying to the lessons
that I learned every single time so
that's it for week four of this
challenge I'll see you you guys next
week where I'm going to be attempting to
turn a hundred dollars into a million
dollar challenge in under 60 days if
you're new to my channel and you want to
be part of the center forget family or
my students and my new Traders are
making anywhere from a thousand to a
thousand five hundred dollars a week as
a beginner set and forget Trader using
my seven figure strategy make sure to
hit the link in the description below
there's a video that explains absolutely
everything and I appreciate you guys
watching this video all the way to the
end I'll see you guys next week because
this challenge is getting good